# Madalina-Eleonora Gheorghe

Bucharest, Bucharest, Romania



madalinaeleonora.gheorghe@gmail.com



0768792728



linkedin.com/in/madalinaeleonorag

# **Summary**

I am a senior Frontend Developer with a long experience working with Angular and RxJs. Additional, I have experience working with React.js, Sass, AWS Services and Azure. I delivered unique features in the past projects, improving user experience, contributing actively in meetings with suggestions and helping other colleagues, maintaining a good communication with the client. My past clients were large companies, in industries like banking, insurance, retail and e-commerce.

## **Experience**



#### Application Engineer / Frontend Developer

Cognizant Softvision

Jan 2023 - Present (2 months)

### Pelcitte. Consultant / Frontend Developer

Deloitte Digital Romania

Oct 2021 - Dec 2022 (1 year 3 months)

1## Internal banking and insurance applications (10.2021 - 01.2022)

Alpha Team - United Kingdom (Banking, Insurance)

Technologies: Angular, RxJs, Jira

☑# Feature that show to the user the active policies into a responsive and interactive design.

☑# Improved the user authentication flow and added more layers of security for the confidential information;

☑# Adding the possibility of a Mid Term Adjustment to a policy.

2## Internal banking application for client loans (02.2022 - 12.2022)

Germany (Banking)

Technologies: React, Thymeleaf, Mambu, moment.js, TypeScript, AWS Services, Java.

☑# Created new React components and uploaded them into Mambu;

# **IBM** Frontend Developer

**IBM** 

Mar 2019 - Oct 2021 (2 years 8 months)

1## Reinsurance internal application (03/2019 - 03/2020)

Germany (Reinsurance)

Technologies: Angular, Ionic, TypeScript, Capacitor, RxJs

☑# I investigated and solved packages vulnerabilities from the applications;

☑# Delivered responsive designs for intern users of the company;

∠
# Worked abroad from Germany with the local team once a month for a better collaboration.

2## Public website for retail recyclable materials (03/2020 - 03/2020)

United Kingdom (Retail)

# 03/2020 - 03/2020

Technologies: React.js

3## Public e-commerce website (04/2020 - 10/2021)

United States (E-Commerce)

Technologies: Angular, TypeScript, RxJs, Adobe Experience Manager, VirtualBox

☑# Being part of the team in a microfrontrend team, delivering shopping list, product pages and cart functionalities;

#### **IBM** Intern

**IBM** 

Dec 2018 - Feb 2019 (3 months)

0## Internship (12/2018 - 02/2019)

Technologies: Angular, Ionic, TypeScript, Capacitor, RxJs

☑# I learned the basics of Ionic and Angular

☑# Applied the knowledge in a project delivered to the client

☑# Designing mobile-based features, working in an agile team.

# RG Practicant - Drive your future

Renault Group

Jun 2017 - Sep 2017 (4 months)

☑# Database maintenance using my own Matlab scripts

#### **Education**



#### 🥯 Universitatea Româno-Americană din București

Master's degree, Computer Science for Economics

2018 - 2020

I've assimilated informations about IOT, mobile applications development, web technologies, AI, GDPR,

PL/SQL, BigData, project management, WordPress, security of computer networks and E-Commerce.

Those knowledges are proved by the projects worked for the graduation of the course.



#### 🥯 Universitatea Româno-Americană din București

Licentiate degree, Computer Science for Economics

2015 - 2018

The knowledge is supported by practical projects to prove a good assimilation of basic information.

These are both economics, such as management, economics, statistics, accounting, office, marketing, econometrics and programming in various languages such as C ++, C # (Console and Windows Forms), Access databases, SQL, HTML, PHP.

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- Enterprise Design Thinking Practitioner IBM
- **IBM Agile Explorer** IBM
- JavaScript Front End Development IBM
- **IBM Mentor** IBM
- Watson and Cloud Foundations IBM
- Think Like a Hacker IBM
- **EF Set Score C1 Advanced** EF Standard English Test (EF SET)
- Angular (Intermediate) Certificate HackerRank 502d54979ed0
- Agile Fundamentals: Including Scrum and Kanban 2022 Udemy UC-e30408dc-436b-467e-9d31-daa12d98ea06

#### Skills

TypeScript • Ionic Framework • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Front-End Development • Analytical Skills • JavaScript • Project Management • Research • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Adobe Photoshop

#### **Honors & Awards**



#### 1st place for Web&Mobile Challenge at DevHacks

Nov 2018

Our result should allows candidates from Romania the possibility to offer reviews/ratings to companies about key areas such as:

- recruitment process
- work environment (team, schedule, etc)
- trainings, learning and development opportunities
- salary & benefits
- work-life balance
- management
- internal systems (procedures, values, way of working)
- other relevant areas

The aim of this product is to help candidates find the employer that best suits their needs and personality, something different.

The target audience of the product will be made up students and young professionals.



# 2nd place at Rau-DevHack Hackathon

Apr 2019

Creating an application to help users choose the most recommended photographer for their event, according to their visual preferences, budget and period, giving photographers easier management on the event calendar and applications.